

+37062444773

Junior Front-End Developer msmykolas@gmail.com

Vilnius

Mykolas Stramkauskas

Profile

I am a passionate and quickly learning starter in React.js and TypeScript with a certificate from a JavaScript (Front-End) course. Before I decided to become a Front-End Developer I worked as QA Specialist. I decided to change my position because I was always interested in coding, knew some of it from self-learning. Finally, I decided to fully commit to it by completing JavaScript course.

Education

JavaScript (Front-End), Vilnius Coding School, Vilnius

02/2023-03/2023

In this course, I have developed skills for theoretical knowledge and practical skills in JavaScript including React.js and TypeScript. I know how to work with Figma design using HTML, CSS and Bootstrap and create functionality with JavaScript, React and TypeScript.

Employment History

QA Specialist at CoinGate

10/2021-06/2022

- Manual testing of front end and back end tickets
- · Writing bug reports on JIRA
- · API testing with Postman
- Testing Woocommerce, PrestaShop and Opencart plugins

Technical Support Specialist at CoinGate

06/2021-06/2022

- Installing and configuring computer systems and applications within the company
- Installing hardware parts for laptops
- Responding to technical queries
- Troubleshooting software and hardware issues

Customer Support Specialist at CoinGate

03/2021-10/2021

- Responding to customer queries via Zendesk and live chat
- · Working with Compliance and Payments teams
- · Working with JIRA tickets

Links

<u>Linkedin</u> <u>Github</u>

Skills

React TypeScript HTML5/CSS, Javascript Bootstrap Quality Assurance JIRA Technical Support

Languages

Lithuanian Native speaker
English Highly proficient